So the plan that I am going to show you now is
called Gift Select
Plus. So, the benefit of this plan is that this
plan is basically
Gift Select Plus of ISI potential. So,
in this plan, there is a plan combining both Gift Select and Gold
products. So, I am giving
an example, like if we take the age of life insurance,
35 years premium payment term,
12 years premium,
30 years
premium 4500 including GST, along with that the
premium for Gold products is
6 years premium, after that the premium will decrease from next year,
GST will be 10
times of this amount. This is the first benefit. So, if we take it, then
in 35 years, for example, suppose
their policy has started at this age, then
they will get immediate instant income at 50. There is
flexibility in instant income. So,
what is the flexibility,
from 5 years to 50 years, like 5, 10, 15, 25, 30, 40, 40,
45 and 50, so in this way, from 5 years to
50 years, anyone can get it.  You can take income, so
if I have taken it for instant 50, that
too within 6 days, on the day the
policy restarts, they will get the payment for it within 6 days, so they will get
instant income within 6 days, that
means they have been given Rs.
1 lakh, they will get it immediately, okay,
within 6 days, after that their income will continue, they will get it
every year in the amount of Rs. 3705 and
they have to pay premium for 12 years by paying Rs. 1 lakh
till 12 years, okay, okay, there is insurance
coverage in this, anyone can take 7 times or 10 times,
okay, it is flexible, so now let's
see how the benefits are
implemented, okay, so suppose
they have to pay premium for 12 years, but
they are not able to pay premium for 12 years, there they
die in their eighth year or ninth year, then the
premium will stop immediately after death
because there is a premium waiver of
benefit in this, the customer will not have to pay the full premium, the
company will pay the premium for the number of years that was left and after that
they will get the death claim immediately, okay, so
how much will be the death claim now  We have caught 10 times
10 times, okay, so their
premium is one lakh rupees, one lakh rupees premium,
they will get 10 times lakh rupees here, they are
paying premium every year at one lakh, okay, they are
paying premium at one lakh,
okay, then
they will get a death claim of 10 lakh rupees here,
okay, they will get 10 lakh rupees as death claim
immediately, okay, they will get it
immediately and the premium will be waived off,
they will
not have to pay the premium in future, okay, so they had to
pay the premium for 12 years, till then if they die after one year
or die anytime in 12 years, then
their premium will be waived off immediately
and they will get the death claim immediately,
but the policy will continue, the policy will continue,
see
what is the second benefit written here, it is written
guaranteed tax income will continue till end
of the term, means after death,
even after receiving the death claim, the income will continue till the end
of the term,
they will keep getting income for the number of years, that
too is guaranteed, that too is tax free.
What is it and I told you that the death claim is already payable,
immediate death claim will be given to them immediately,
okay, what is the fourth benefit,
maturity, if they are alive then they will get maturity, even if they die then also
they will get
maturity, we
can say death claim, where any company
's policy death claim, then the
policy ends
after getting the death claim, but here
even after getting the death claim, they are getting maturity
claim as well and they will keep getting the income, which is
continuous income, till the end of
the term, you are seeing it,
okay, and there is a flexible match option
also in this, if the customer wants to take 100% match, then whatever
premium he has paid for the year, i.e.
one lakh, if he has paid premium for 12 years, if he has paid premium for
12 years, then he
can take Rs. 12 lakh at maturity, but
here we are waiting for 12 lakh, the
customer can take it at 110% here also, 11
%  Customers can take it here at 120 as well.
Customers can take it here at 130, at
144, at 150, at 160, at 170, at 180,
at 190 and at 200. Customers can take any option,
so we have taken 100% 100% here, which
means if the customer has given Rs 12 lakh, then
he is getting Rs 12 lakh. Okay, so in this plan,
if the customer remains alive, then
how much is he getting every year for the one lakh that he is giving?
He got Rs 50000 within 6 days,
so he got instant income of
50000 here
within 6 days, plus he is getting income every year at Rs
3705, he gets tax free income every year at Rs
3705, so if he does not die and
remains alive, then he will keep getting it for the entire 30 years at Rs
3705, this amount is complete.
They will keep getting it for 30 years of the term,
so if they die, then
their death premium will be waived immediately, the
customer and any family member of the customer will not have to pay any premium
and
they will immediately get ₹ lakh, 10 times the premium paid, ₹ lakh,
even after that they will
not have to pay any premium, even if they have received ₹ lakh,
their income will continue and they will
get it again in marriage, so this is gold
production, gold
protection, so today this goal protection,
today we have many goals in life, for example, let's say
higher education of the child,
marriage of the child, our retirement, our
family dependents, those who
live for them,
their food, everything is
dependent on us, so we can maintain that too with this plan, so
this plan has everything, so
this benefit is the best, even
after death, their
income continues even after receiving the death claim
and  You don't have to pay premium and you are
also getting benefits, so this plan
is currently India's number one plan, ICICI
Prudential's Gift Select Plus. If
you want any quotation today, you
can send me the two numbers given to them.
I will give you the quotation based on your date of birth and the premium you want to pay.
You can also take advice from the videos that I have sent you. Thank you so
much. So, whatever you see in the video, the plan
's details are of ICS Potential's Gift
Select Plus.
Whatever goals we have in life, like child's
education, higher education, child's marriage,
we have many other goals in life
which we keep on doing to maintain our family, so
we will be able to complete all those goals if we are
in it, even if we are not there, if we remain alive, we continue to do so.
Today, on Women's Day, the
best gift is for those whom we
love, for whom we are
maintaining our family,
give them this gift today itself for their future. Thank you so much.
So today's women's day best plan
ICC portal gift select plus to
hi
plan jivane kich gol gol protect kar plan ev ta gar uy to ne
udaah life
i 35 yrs means zero ba bar din p to baran
bas premium de 12 bar and policy term 30
bar eva
premium raar go prkne
jis aur gu to ki
befit
to
bit to
premium sange sang 50 instant
income 5 sa din bank aka chale ja to
% bank chale
income pension lele income aur cric
income tax le se but
3705 gains tax free per savings savings bank
next 30 do number ho ja increasing income
option tax le but compound interest at 5 pence compound interest at 5 pence compound
income at 5 pence listen einstein proverb today's first
biggest interest ji eighth compound
compound interest bole to today's income
per compound income inam inam income
kan to
match match
premium match f
par match
ama to  If someone
dies, if the
premium is stopped
then the premium of the firm will be paid
death claim 10 times 10
times, that is, lakh to 10 lakh rupees to the family, then the
income of the entire company policy is
closed policy, if the policy is closed then the income of the policy is given in these policies
and the
policy is given in these policies minimum
premium 500 instant income
flex
% instant income 5 10% on 30% then this
income depends on choose %
interest level
income per day
and increase income in
per % cycle
income
match goal protect if death happens along with death
claim
premium family ke income kanye le le im
match so today bo aani
apna parivar keise aai
pril gif select plus
please like kar channel subscribe kar bell
icon dele and jnana ko video
thank you